[
  {
    "question": "What percentage of Cefixime may lose its potency upon UV light exposure?",
    "options": ["2-3%", "5-6%", "8-9%", "12-15%"],
    "correct_option": "8-9%"
  },
  {
    "question": "Efficacy of Esomeprazole capsule reduces by what percentage range while taking with food?",
    "options": ["20–30%", "30–40%", "43–53%", "55–65%"],
    "correct_option": "43–53%"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is described as 'Powerful Yet Gentle'?",
    "options": ["Dinovo", "Frenxit", "Numira", "Vivori"],
    "correct_option": "Numira"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the components used in Napa Extend for Hydrophilic Matrix Systems?",
    "options": [
      "Maize starch and Carnauba Wax",
      "Benecel K15M and Methocel K4MCR",
      "Opadry II and Aqua II",
      "Glucose and Talc"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Benecel K15M and Methocel K4MCR"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many vitamins and minerals does Bextram Silver contain?",
    "options": ["20", "25", "30", "35"],
    "correct_option": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "Remmo is the only Esomeprazole brand with which distinct feature?",
    "options": [
      "Single mode of action",
      "Dual-mode of actions with immediate acid neutralization and long-lasting acid suppression",
      "Sugar-free and gluten-free",
      "Film-coated layer for delayed release"
    ],
    "correct_option": "Dual-mode of actions with immediate acid neutralization and long-lasting acid suppression"
  },
  {
    "question": "Exposure to any irritant or allergen may cause ________.",
    "options": ["Fever", "Dry Cough", "Drowsiness", "Skin rash"],
    "correct_option": "Dry Cough"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which BPL brand can be prescribed for depression in post-menopausal women due to hormonal imbalance?",
    "options": ["Vivori", "Frenxit", "Numira", "Napa Extend"],
    "correct_option": "Frenxit"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the pediatric dose of Triocim in Typhoid?",
    "options": [
      "10 mg/kg/day for 7 days",
      "15 mg/kg/day for 10 days",
      "20 mg/kg/day up to 14 days",
      "25 mg/kg/day for 5 days"
    ],
    "correct_option": "20 mg/kg/day up to 14 days"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which trial showed that Amlodipine group has up to 15% RRR in development of renal impairment compared with Atenolol?",
    "options": ["ASCOT-BPLA Trial", "ICHE Trial", "NAPLEX Trial", "BRIGHT Study"],
    "correct_option": "ASCOT-BPLA Trial"
  }
]
